# ADLENE

## FELIACHI

https://www.linkedin.com/in/adlene-feliachi/



#### CONTACT

+213 560 54 48 89 adlafeliachi@gmail.com Said Hamdine - Algiers

### **PROFILE**

Holder of a Master's degree in Automation and Industrial Computing, I am determined to apply my technical skills to projects in my area of expertise or in the IT sector, with the aim of contributing to effective

https://myportfolio-adlene.web.app/

#### **EDUCATION**

#### MASTER'S DEGREE IN AUTOMATION O COMPUTER SCIENCE TEACHER AND INDUSTRIAL COMPUTING

2019 - 2021

University M'hamed Bougara Boumerdès - Algeria

#### O MECHATRONICS EDUCATION

2017 - 2018

Belgorod State Technological University named after V.G. Shukhov.

#### O BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN **ELECTRONICS AND AUTOMATION**

2013 - 2016

University of Science and Technology (USTHB)

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Bouchaoui High School (February 2024 - June 2024)

#### O WEB DESIGNER

Digital Smile (July 2023 - October 2023)

- Creation of the company website https://digital-smile.vercel.app/
- Working with graphic tools (Photoshop Illustrator Figma)

#### O OPERATIONS MANAGER

Intertrade LLC (September 2022 - February 2023)

- Ensure coordination between the delivery team and the call center team and intervene when necessary
- Ensure injections of new orders into the ECOTRACK CRM as well as changing packages status

#### **SKILLS**

#### Javascript











Github





PowerPoint

#### O OUALITY ASSURANCE ENGINEER

Sig Service (November 2021 - January 2022)

#### O RUSSIAN LANGUAGE TEACHER - LEVEL A1.2

Language Research School (October 2019 - January 2020)

#### O CALL CENTER OPERATOR

Waves Call (February 2015 - August 2015)

#### LANGUAGES

- Arabic - Native Russian - Native
- French - Fluent
- English Fluent

### INTERNSHIP

#### ○ MASTER'S THESIS

Observation and Prediction Glucose of Blood Concentration for Diabetes Type-1

#### O BACHELOR'S THESIS

Design and operation of a three-story elevator